Amish Saturday night Manish 239 people or feared dead after a jetliner pound for Beijing disappear as English family member
阿米什星期六晚上和Manish 239人或一客机每磅北京后遇难消失的英国家庭成员
worthit2u of a pastor's were traveling with stolen passports deep into the mystery of the faith of Malaysia flight 370
一个牧师的的worthit2u与被盗护照在旅行深入到马来西亚飞行370的真道的奥秘
cameras that catch drivers running red lights white mothers can't wait to install them
那赶闯红灯白人母亲的驱动相机迫不及待地安装它们
epic battle 2500 square of America spelling bee at last so long tonight 8 little letters and it all
史诗战役的美国拼字比赛2500万，最后只要今晚8小信而这一切
NBC News world headquarters in New York
NBC新闻全球总部设在纽约
NBC Nightly News with Lester Holt
NBC晚间新闻与莱斯特·霍尔特
good evening in this house Sunday in Southeast Asia were in the light of a new day a massive multinational searches in full swing
晚上好，在这所房子周日在东南亚是在新的一天了大规模的跨国企业搜索的光如火如荼
Remo lesion jetliner did vanish not quite 36 hours ago with 239 people onboard including for Americans in Malaysia Airlines Boeing triple 7 was traveling from Kuala Lumpur to Beijing
雷莫病变客机没有消失不太36小时前239船上的人包括美国人在马来西亚航空公司的一架波音三联7从吉隆坡前往北京
what all contact with lost over open water
什么所有的接触失去了开放水域
roughly halfway between Malaysia and the southern tip of Vietnam
马来西亚和越南南端大约一半之间
B&C search now includes an American Navy warship the hunt for wreckage now centered on Fuel slicks
B＆C的搜索现在包括美国的海军军舰追捕残骸现在集中在燃料光头胎
spot on the surface of the sea 104 cause tingling the possibility of foul play is not partly focused on 2 mystery passengers traveling on stolen passport there a lot of angles to cover here we begin with Tom Costello are Washington newsroom Tom what's the latest
海104事业刺痛犯规的可能性表面斑点是不是部分集中在2神秘乘客被盗护照有很多角度来采访的，我们开始与汤姆·科斯特洛是华盛顿编辑部汤姆有什么最新的
Hollister Malaysia Airlines says this plane was last inspector just 10 days ago and it wasn't proper condition their words at this hour does naval units
霍利斯特马来西亚航空公司说，这架飞机最后一次检查只需10天前，这是不妥当的条件下他们的话在这个时候做海军部队
countries are listening should be coming from the plains emergency transmitters in an area where the Vietnamese military believes in a pound an important clue
国家正在听应该从平原紧急发射器在一个地区，在一斤越南军方认为，一个重要的线索来
both Acosta Vietnam to the water may provide the best hope for finding Malaysia Airlines flight 370
既阿科斯塔越南水可以提供的最大希望寻找马来西亚航空公司飞行370
the plane live Kuala Lumpur at 12:40 a.m. Saturday the red eye flight to Beijing with 239 passengers and crew on board among them
飞机住吉隆坡在12:40上午星期六红眼航班到北京有239名乘客和船员在船上其中
Philip would an IBM executive 11 to 2 hours into the flight at 35000 feet air traffic controllers lost contact with the planes
菲利普将IBM的高管11至2小时到飞行在35000英尺空中交通管制员失去联系的飞机
where over the Gulf of Thailand veteran crash investigation into a routine flight
在那里的泰国老将坠毁调查一次例行飞行海湾
whatever happened with catastrophic an incapacitated the airplane such that the crew couldn't get a mayday call of
什么灾难性的无行为能力的飞机发生了这样的人员无法得到一个呼叫五月天
the plains of Boeing triple 7 200 series nearly 12 years old middle age for planes in August 2012 what's the tip of a wing after clipping another plane on the ground in Shanghai the when was fixed but did that contribute to the accident
波音三联7 200系列近12岁的中年用于飞机2012年8月平原什么是机翼的尖端裁剪另一架飞机在地面上在上海的时候被固定后，却并有助于事故
Captain John Cox
队长约翰·考克斯
what are the early signs that he's already underway is thorough review of all the maintenance records of the airplane
什么是早期迹象表明，他已经开始为飞机的所有维修记录的全面审查
if the airplane has sustained damage is it getting this is round incident that is something that certainly be investigators are going to look at
如果飞机已经持续伤害是它得到这是一轮事件，是值得肯定会被调查人员要看看
we do know the captain was experience does a Harley Ahmad Shah was 50 years old with 18
我们知道队长是经验做了哈雷艾哈迈德·沙阿是50岁与18
looking for buddy's to share the specimen
寻找好友的分享试样
the first officer with 27 year old free comedy with 2800 hours of experience adding to the mystery to Europeans on a passenger manifest
与27岁免费的喜剧2800小时的经验增加了神秘欧洲人在旅客名单副驾驶
safe and sound on the ground butta reported their passport stolen in Thailand 12 years ago USM Malaysian authorities are now looking at the who used a stolen passports to board a plane and what were they go up to
安然无恙地上BUTTA报告了他们的护照被盗，在泰国12年前USM马来西亚当局现正于谁用偷来的护照登机，什么是他们上去
two people travel on falls passports when a plane disappears from radar really get people's attention as a check
两个人就跌倒护照旅行时，飞机从雷达消失，真正得到人们的关注，因为检查
the plane that sells has a very strong safety record the crash of Asiana 214 in San Francisco Lexol I was the triple sevens first brutal accident investigators believe that was pilot error
卖飞机具有非常强的安全纪录韩亚214在旧金山LEXOL崩溃我是三重七人榄球赛第一残酷的事故调查人员相信，这是飞行员操作失误
via media challenge now finding the wreckage of militia 370 in the waters of Vietnam
通过媒体的挑战，现在发现民兵370的残骸在越南水域
this is a really similar to the crash of Air France flight 447 which disappeared in the Atlantic in 2009 200 years to find the record at the bottom of the ocean
这是一个非常类似的法航447航班坠毁而消失在大西洋，2009年200年的查找记录在海洋的底部
wall search teams will be looking for black boxes we here so much about their also going to be examined the size of the debris field if they find one if its why that was a just a plane broke up in flight condensed Takamine the plane remain intact until impact of the water or perhaps the ground
墙搜索队会找黑盒子，我们这里这么多关于他们的也将被检查碎片场的大小，如果他们发现一个，如果它的原因，这是一个只是一个平面分手的飞行高峰凝结在飞机保持不变，直到水的冲击或者接地
alright thanks and 2/3 of Arizona border missing plane are from China tonight in Beijing to strong families and friends of gather data hotel to wait for answers CNBC is there and joints with more units
好吧感谢和亚利桑那州边境失踪飞机的2/3，今晚是从中国北京来收集数据的酒店稳固的家庭和朋友，等待答案CNBC是存在的，关节与更多的单位
is wearing thin about 36 hours after flight mh3 70 went missing 200 the family members and friends of the passengers have the holdup in the hotel behind knee
穿着单薄约36小时后飞行MH3 70失踪乘客的200家庭成员和朋友都滞留在膝盖后面的酒店
airline to set up a makeshift Crisis Center about 100 Airlines Stafford have arrived the family who are just waiting for any information about their loved ones in any gear feel that they been left in the dark in a demanding more frequent updates
航空公司设立一个临时危机中心约100航空公司斯塔福德已经抵达谁只是在等待他们的亲人在任何档位任何信息的家人觉得他们被留在黑暗中，要求更频繁的更新
from the airline of people are starting to lose hope they might not see their family members alive again
从人们的航空公司都开始失去希望，他们可能不会再看到他们的家人还活着
airline Authority at the rescue operation in the South China Sea is still on going to the USS battleship an aircraft 2
航空管理局在中国南海救援行动仍在进行到USS战舰飞机2
the area and China has also sent in naval vessel with the Sun rising the Air Mission which has a suspended over night has no resume as government and people continue to hope to find any signs of the missing plane
该地区和中国也派出了在舰艇与太阳升起的空中任务其中有一个悬浮在晚上没有简历政府和人民继续希望能找到失踪飞机的任何迹象
force in Beijing thank you
北京力谢谢
NBC News aviation expert and former airline pilot John Cox NBC News counterterrorism analyst Michael Leiter don't let me start with you we keep hearing about this possibility of catastrophic breakup is there anything short of an explosion of the plane coming apart
NBC新闻航空专家和前航空公司飞行员约翰·考克斯NBC新闻的反恐分析师迈克尔·雷特不要让我从你开始，我们不断听到灾难性解体的这种可能性是有什么短的平面散乱爆炸
explain a sudden and complete loss of communications
说明通信突然和完全丧失
what are there several possibilities erase something as simple as a major electrical problem could mean that the airplane could not transmit I couldn't be seen on radar so it's very early this stage to draw conclusions
什么是有几种可能性抹掉一些简单的作为一个主要的电气问题可能意味着飞机不能传输我无法看到雷达所以它是非常早期的阶段得出结论
the debris field could very well telephone what the size of the debris field and how it has interacted with the Wynns with a white or components papers and things for example in comparison to the heavier objects such as the landing gear or engines
碎片场很可能电话机什么碎片场的大小和它是如何相互作用的威力狮与白色或组件文件和活动，例如相比于更重的物体，如起落架或引擎
Michael trouble getting my head wrapped in a post 911 world you can get on an airplane with a stolen passport 10 and 12 years ago but that's sad what kind of blonde bells has that started ringing at at intelligence agencies around the world
迈克尔麻烦我的头上包着后911的世界你可以在飞机上用偷来的护照10年和12年以前，但是那是可悲的是什么样的金发铃铛都有在开始在世界各地的情报机构铃声
Lester definitely change towel intelligence organizations in the US and global look at this prior to the stolen passport issued this was a tragedy but folks mostly sad
莱斯特绝对改变毛巾情报组织在美国和全球的看看这个前发行的护照被盗，这是一个悲剧，但人们大多是悲伤
probably something mechanical with the plane with this there's at least one element which make some very concerned they know that people were on that plane who shouldn't have been using this paper
可能是一些机械与这个平面上有至少一个元素而做出一些非常关注他们知道，人们就应该使用谁不会被这种纸张平面
what they don't know is what they were up to where they simply criminals were using stolen passport or were they on that plane to do something at various and that's where the intelligence community are dating now
他们不知道的是，他们最多，他们只是被犯罪分子利用偷来的护照还是他们上飞机做一些不同，这就是那里的情报界现在约会
John this was an overnight flight it's a pretty heavy traffic root down aja 35000 feet of the clear would you expect at another Cruyff seen some kind of a flash
约翰·这是一个通宵飞行这是一个相当沉重的交通根部向下AJA35000英尺明确的，你会期望在另一克鲁伊夫看到一些闪光的
Heather Bennett explosion
希瑟贝内特爆炸
explosion would be debris that guy could be seen by potentially some long range radar there will be another reports of ships or
爆炸将碎片家伙可能由潜在的一些远程雷达可以看出会有船的另一报告或
aircraft so I'm a I'm not convinced it all we got an implied explosion Here I think we're going to Warren Moore as the course of the day goes on and the the Ariel search begins to put together this debris field
飞机，所以我一个我不相信这一切，我们得到了一个隐含的爆炸在这里，我觉得我们要沃伦·摩尔作为一天的课程的推移和阿里尔搜索开始拼凑这些碎片场
John Cox Michael I want to turn out of the crisis in Ukraine new level today is Russia send even more troops in the Crimean Peninsula NBC's in Williamsville
约翰·迈克尔·考克斯我想打开走出危机在乌克兰新台阶今天是俄罗斯派在克里米亚半岛NBC的威廉斯维尔甚至更多的部队
Independence Square today demanding Russia leave Primea symbol Scorpius to be reinforced amount convoys on the move
独立广场当今要求苛刻的俄罗斯留下PRIMEA天蝎座的符号进行加固量车队在移动
hours of the Russian soldiers briefly seize control of the Ukrainian base that still blocking others
俄罗斯士兵小时简要抓住乌克兰基础，仍然阻挡他人的控制
promiscuous Ortiz oral remaining Ukrainian soldiers in Crimea
在克里米亚混杂奥尔蒂斯口腔剩余乌克兰士兵
surrender with mini reviews security monitors to be prevented from entering the peninsula
投降了迷你的评论安防监视器将进入防止半岛
armed man farting warning shot into the air with automatic weapons in Russian speaking East Ukraine proboscis protest discounted jewelry to Russia the theories that Russia's staring up trouble to justify intervention in this region 2
全副武装的人放屁警告射击到空气自动武器在讲俄语东乌喙抗议打折的珠宝俄罗斯，俄罗斯的盯着起来麻烦的理论在这一地区2有理由干预
who is here is very volatile there is a concern about and Benson kiss mean everybody would welcome in Moscow
是谁在这里是很不稳定有关于和本森的吻意味着每个人都关注的问题欢迎在莫斯科
old is hockey if it was plenty of fear and uncertainty Olga told me that everybody's worried but she said we should stick together in there should be no bloodshed
旧是曲棍球，如果它是大量的恐惧和不确定性奥尔加告诉我，每个人都在担心，但她说，我们应该团结在一起的应该没有流血
Alexander was playing angry extremist seizing control in Kiev what he told me independent country Russia now should stay away people in the East what Russian television which depicts Ukraine's revolution is a neo fascist cool
亚历山大在玩愤怒的极端分子夺取控制在基辅什么，他告诉我，独立的国家俄罗斯现在应该远离的人在东什么俄罗斯电视台描绘了乌克兰的革命是一个新法西斯酷
militant right wing groups are a minority what they do have seats in the new government vehicles that played in outside the barricades in Estill bear
激进右翼团体是少数他们做了什么在新的政府车辆席位充当路障外埃斯蒂尔熊
the flowers hear a fresh but so the tires barricades been turned into a memorial
花听到一个新鲜的，但这样的轮胎路障被辟为纪念馆
the fortifications ons going to be taken away anytime soon petrol bombs remain at the ready
工事组件将被带往很快消失汽油弹留在准备
leader of 14 write a militia told me its not over on the barricades few people appear to trust the interim government
14写领袖的民兵告诉我，它不是过度的路障少数人会出现信任临时政府
told me ultimately we control the government anyway
告诉我，最终我们反正控制政府
the interim government has real challenges ahead is it calls for unity in the face of Russian aggression in Williams NBC News Kiev
临时政府有真正的挑战是它要求在统一俄罗斯侵略威廉姆斯NBC新闻基辅的脸
President Obama made phone cost a day to remember of European leaders on the crisis in Ukraine NBC's Kristen Welker is traveling with the president in Florida were the first family is spending the weekend
奥巴马总统的电话花费一个值得纪念的日子欧洲领导人在乌克兰NBC的克里斯汀·韦尔克危机正行驶在佛罗里达州的总统是第一个家庭是消费的周末
tensions mountain in Ukraine the White House is taking
张力山在乌克兰白宫正在采取
pantie show the president Obama is still engaged in the diplomatic efforts to get Russian forces to retreat to the bases in Crimea late this afternoon the White House release a photo of President Obama
短裤展现总统奥巴马仍在从事外交努力，以获得俄罗斯军队撤退到克里米亚基地今天下午晚些时候，白宫发布奥巴马总统的照片
who reached out to several of his town apart Silverstein among the prime minister of the UK as well as leaders of France Italy and the Baltic Lithuania Latvia
谁伸出他的几个镇西尔弗斯坦除了英国和总理之间的法国意大利和波罗的海立陶宛拉脱维亚领导人
bob is trying to build a strong national television and depression Mr puja retreat Africa right now we're falling on deaf ears in Russia
鲍勃正试图建立一个强大的国家电视台和抑郁先生闭关法会非洲现在我们落在聋子的耳朵在俄罗斯
White House official reiterated the president insisted that Russia allow international observer and human rights monitors into Crimea
白宫官员重申，总统坚持认为，俄罗斯允许国际观察员，人权监测到克里米亚
no better an ambassador Dennis Ross is President Obama is playing the longest to get in Crimea with the ideas to build up another International Car Show to prevent you from going into other parts of Ukraine
没有更好的大使丹尼斯·罗斯是美国总统奥巴马正在播放最长得到在克里米亚的想法建立另一个国际车展，以防止你进入乌克兰的其它部分
today the president South Carolina mother accused of trying to kill her 3 children by driving them in the ocean in Daytona Beach Florida made her first court appearance
今天总统南卡罗来纳州的母亲指控试图驾驶他们在代托纳比奇佛罗里达州的海洋杀了她3个孩子做了她第一次出庭
for Albany Wilkerson which set of 1.2 million dollars to use charge with 3 counts of attempted murder and child abuse
奥尔巴尼威尔克森其设置为1.2亿美元使用费一项企图谋杀控罪和虐待儿童
Saturdays in red light cam 4 are going up in some places
在红灯凸轮4周六打算在一些地方
American spelling bee afternoon
美国拼字比赛下午
InTown cities and states across America a debate is now raging over those cameras that snap a picture when you run a red light you then get a ticket in the mail usually when I have to find some places have decided to turn them off
位于InTown城市和全美州辩论正在激烈了那些拍摄照片的相机，当你闯红灯，那么你买到票的邮件通常当我必须要找到一些地方已经决定将其关闭
others are buying more of them I report from NBC's Kristen Dahlgren
其他从NBC的克里斯汀·达尔格伦购买更多的人我汇报
running a red light nobody argues it isn't dangerous
闯红灯没人认为它是没有危险
but there is now a huge to be about weather cameras to catch offenders
但现在有一个巨大的是关于天气的相机捕捉罪犯
America's intersection
美国的十字路口
Brick Township New Jersey one of the first places to get the cameras BAM
第一个地方得到相机的BAM砖乡新泽西州1
mayor they werent making intersections safer crashes actually increase 400 brick is in a loan on Thursday St Petersburg Florida pull the plug on its cameras after 30 years did make physical cent
市长他们werent使交叉口安全事故实际上增加了400砖是在贷款上周四圣彼得堡佛罗里达州30年后拔出其摄像头插头没做物理仙
im Wednesday Ellisville Missouri voted to terminate contract after public outcry
IM周三埃利斯维尔密苏里州投票舆论哗然后终止合同
critic city cameras are unconstitutional
评论家城市摄像机是违宪
create a driving hazard
创建一个危险驾驶
people really tough spot between making a choice to prep student a rear end accident or force themselves to run at intersection and get a ticket
人们作出选择学生预习的后端事故或强迫自己在交叉运行，并得到一张票之间真的很难现货
nationwide the number of communities using red light cameras down about 6 percent
全国范围内使用冲红灯摄影机下降约6％的社区的数量
2012 animal 24 states in Washington DC allow them nine states have banned
2012动物在华盛顿特区24个州允许他们九个国家已禁止使用
so we're coming after the first one right now St Louis police chief in his city has no no increasing crashes 500 violations a day
所以我们在第一个之后要来，现在在他的城市圣路易斯警察局长有否增加500崩溃侵犯了一天
and then we have another Vilas nossa nossa
然后我们有另一个维拉斯诺萨诺萨
Dustin says without the cameras his force would be stretched to 10
达斯汀说，没有摄像头他的力量会被拉伸到10
it would take over 200 police officers to do with a camera doing today hair grease with the camera providers statistics Asians are working
这将需要超过200名警察做用相机做今天的头发油脂用相机提供的统计数据亚洲人工作
more than 90 percent of the people that run red lights don't get another ticket they don't do it again
90％以上的闯红灯的人没有得到另一张机票，他们不要再这样做
mix
混合
I'm in a different Public Safety
我在不同的公共安全
is it sinful to God movie Graham
它是有罪的神格雷厄姆电影
to the debate like these drivers is it likely to stop Kristen Dahlgren NBC News St Louis Missouri
像这些司机的辩论是它可能停止克里斯汀·达尔格伦NBC新闻圣路易斯密苏里州
Frankie mom and subordinate Indian jetliner is a real wheel car fire after landing in Nepal all 176 passers in 6 crew members on the flight from New Delhi right back NSYNC doors and are safe no injuries reported the cause of a fire is under investigation
羊羊妈妈和下属的印度客机降落是在尼泊尔所有176路人的6名机组人员来自新德里的航班右后卫NSYNC的门后，一个真正的四轮汽车火灾和安全暂无伤亡报道火灾的原因正在调查中
coming up a war hero receives an altar long overdue
来了一位战争英雄接收到一个祭坛姗姗来迟
going home
回家
you going to stay here and face the fellas
你要在这里停留和面对的小伙子们
actress Sheila MacRae start on Broadway and in films what was best known for playing Alice Kramden opposite Jackie Gleason's Ralph in the 1960's recreation of The Honeymooners TV show her family confirm she died Thursday at 92 years old
女演员希拉·麦克雷开始在百老汇和电影中什么最出名的是扮演爱丽丝Kramden对面杰基格利森的拉尔夫在1960年的娱乐蜜月旅行电视的显示她的家人确认，她周四在92岁去世
and Carmen Berra has died she was the wife of New York Yankees Legend Yogi Berra Way just celebrating 65th wedding anniversary in January and their marriage was central to the Broadway play Bronx Bombers that just closed
和卡门贝拉已经死了，她是纽约洋基队传奇约吉贝拉路刚庆祝65周年结婚纪念日一月的妻子，他们的婚姻是中央的百老汇戏剧，刚刚结束布朗克斯轰炸机
band 3 sons 11 grandchildren had a great grandson Carmen Berra was 85 years old
带3个儿子11孙子有一个伟大的孙子卡门·贝拉85岁
rimtyme in 89 year old World War 2 veteran state New York finally received the Medal he deserved today Richard Faulkner was awarded the Purple Heart 70 years
rimtyme 89岁二战老兵州纽约终于收到了勋章，他今天当之无愧的理查德·福克纳被授予紫心70年
battle he was a lone survivor when is b17 bomber collide in midair with another allied plane that crashed in Nazi occupied France
战斗中，他是一个孤独的幸存者时，B17轰炸机碰撞在半空中与纳粹坠毁占领的法国另一面结盟
after 29 days behind enemy lines who made it to safety Amazon offer the Purple Heart buddy the client at that time aqua and receiving an award with others have died now it says he wants his grandchildren have something to remember is military service
后背后是谁做的，以安全亚马逊敌后29天提供了紫心哥们客户当时旱厕和接受一个奖项与其他人已经死了现在说，他希望他的孙子们有话要记住的是兵役
endless reminder to spring forward make sure you turn your clocks ahead 1 hour before you go to bed tonight daylight saving time officially begins at 2 a.m. Steelhead
无尽的提醒，春天正向确保你把你的时钟快1小时，然后再上床​​睡觉，今晚夏令时正式开始在凌晨2点的Steelhead
spell of a champion finely ground
拼出一个冠军细磨的
finally tonight it lasted 2 weeks and took nearly a hundred rounds but we finally have a winner it all went down at a regional spelling bee in Kansas City winter goes into the National Spelling Bee Iron much has the final showdown
今晚终于它持续了2周，花了将近一百回合，但我们终于有了一个赢家这一切在堪萨斯城去了在地区拼字比赛冬天进入全国拼字铁多有最后的摊牌
did Kansas City Missouri it took 95 rounds and 261 words to finally spell WI nner
没密苏里州堪萨斯城花了95回合，261话终于拼出威斯康星新新人类创新
bi County Spelling Bee
双向县拼字比赛
down between 5th grader Sofia Hoffman and 7th grader Kush Sharma battle back and forth word for word 26 letters or only weapons
第五下来年级索菲亚·霍夫曼和七年级学生都库什夏尔马战斗之间来回逐字逐句26个字母或仅武器
the duel started 2 weeks ago 166 round and had to be postponed because officials ran out of approved words to challenge the pumping cost to Justin Boots to nationals
决斗开始2个星期前166圆，不得不被推迟，因为官员跑出批准的话，挑战抽水成本贾斯汀靴国民